<resources>
    
    <string name="app_name">Treece</string>
    <string name="the_game_u"><u>The Game</u></string>   
    <string name="the_game">The Game</string>
    <string name="game_with_a_purpose"><u>Treece</u></string>
    <string name="learning">Learning</string>
    <string name="leave">Exit</string>
    <string name="ranking">Ranking</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="go">Go !</string>
    <string name="new_game">New game</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="top10_title">Top 10</string>
    <string name="rank_header">Rank</string>
    <string name="score_ranking">Score</string>
    <string name="player_ranking">Player</string>
    <string name="rank_1">1.</string>
    <string name="rank_2">2.</string>
    <string name="rank_3">3.</string>
    <string name="rank_4">4.</string>
    <string name="rank_5">5.</string>
    <string name="rank_6">6.</string>
    <string name="rank_7">7.</string>
    <string name="rank_8">8.</string>
    <string name="rank_9">9.</string>
    <string name="rank_10">10.</string>
    <string name="score">Score:</string>
    <string name="level_h">Level:</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="timer_header">Time:</string>
    <string name="timer_over">Time is over !</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="validate">Validate</string>
    <string name="tree_view">Tree view</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="straightOff">Straight Off</string>
    <string name="straightOn">Straight On</string>
    <string name="global_error">GE: </string>
    <string name="local_error">LE: </string>
    <string name="n_scatter">Scatter Plot:</string>
    <string name="page_info">Page: </string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_u"><u>Help</u></string>
    <string name="help_game">The Game mode</string>
    <string name="help_game_u"><u>The Game mode</u></string>
    <string name="help_learning">The Learning mode</string>
    <string name="help_learning_u"><u>The Learning mode</u></string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_u"><u>About</u></string>
    <string name="page_number_game_1">1/4</string>
    <string name="page_number_game_2">2/4</string>
    <string name="page_number_game_3">3/4</string>
    <string name="page_number_game_4">4/4</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_1">1/6</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_2">2/6</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_3">3/6</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_4">4/6</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_5">5/6</string>
    <string name="page_number_learning_6">6/6</string>
    <string name="dialog_msg_score">Do you want enter your score?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_end">Finished</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_first_time_game">How to play the game?</string>
    <string name="dialog_msg_first_time_game">This is the first time you launch
        the application in Game mode. Do you want to go in the help menu in order
        to learn the rules of the game?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_first_time_learning">What is the Learning mode?</string>
    <string name="dialog_msg_first_time_learning">This mode is made for expert in
        machine learning. Do you want to have some information about this mode?</string>
    <string name="dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_no">No</string>
    <string name="dialog_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="dialog_try_again">Try again and do better to enter in the Top 10.</string>
    <string name="dialog_ranking">Ranking</string>
    <string name="dialog_enter_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="dialog_complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="enjoy">Enjoy the game!</string>
    <string name="number_of_instances">Number of instances: </string>
    <string name="number_of_attributes">Number of attributes: </string>
    <string name="number_of_scatter_plot">Number of Scatter Plots: </string>
    <string name="number_of_classes">Number of classes: </string>
    <string name="choose_database">Choose a database</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="network_issue">You need an active connection to the Internet 
        to use this application. Please, turn on your Wifi or mobile data to 
        be connected to Internet.</string>
    <string name="title_network_issue">Internet connection required</string>
    <string name="process_tree">Processing the tree...</string>
    <string name="next_node">Retrieving the next node...</string>
    <string name="build_prev_page">Building the previous page...</string>
    <string name="build_next_page">Building the next page...</string>
    <string name="server_unreachable">Server unreachable</string>
    <string name="server_unreachable_msg">We have a server problem. 
        Please try again later. Thank you for your comprehension.</string>
    <string name="thank_you">You have successfully built the tree. You can
        visualize it by clicking the \"Tree view\" button.\nThank
        you for your help.</string>
    <string name="network_lose_title">Connection lost</string>
    <string name="network_lose_msg">It seems that you may not be connected to the
        Internet anymore. Please check your Wifi connection or your mobile data.</string>
    <string name="root_level">Root level</string>
    <string name="root">Root</string>
    <string name="node">Node</string>
    <string name="node_threshold">Node Threshold</string>
    <string name="left_child">Left Child</string>
    <string name="right_child">Right Child</string>
    <string name="current_node"> (Current Node)</string>
    <string name="current_branch"> (Current Branch)</string>
    <string name="help_game_fragment_0">The purpose of this game is to separate 
        points of color. You have to gather points of the same color together. 
        To do that, your job is to trace a line between these points.</string>
    <string name="help_game_fragment_1">When it is done, you can validate your 
        line and try to do the same with the other part of the image. If you 
        have managed to split points well enough into groups of different color,
        you will reach the next level. You may encounter difficulty in processing 
        some images. In this case, you can skip to the next image.</string> 
    <string name="help_game_fragment_2">A progress bar shows you the proportion 
        of points that are already well enough separated and that will not be 
        shown anymore on the screen. You have a certain amount of time
        to process the images. You begin the game with 20 seconds at the timer.
        Each time you validate your trace, you will gain 2 extra seconds. Time
        is a valuable ressource, be careful with it ! But do not hesitate 
        to skip to an another image: you will see that sometimes it is worth 
        the trouble of losing some resources to get a better situation for 
        splitting. It is mandatory to have points on each side of the line 
        in order to validate it.</string> 
    <string name="help_game_fragment_3">At the beginning of each level, you
        have a stock of 100 points. After each split, this stock decreases by 5
        points. Howewer, if you succeed in creating groups that contains points
        of one color, called pure groups, only 2 points will be removed
        from the stock. In this case, you will see the progress bar fill in.
        At the end of the level, the stock is added to your score. Then, in order
        to maximize your score, do your best to reduce the number of splits and
        build as more pure groups as possible.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_0">This mode is designed for experts in
        machine learning. It allows the user to build a decision tree for a database
        he has chosen. This decision tree is used as a model to classify 
        data (or objects).</string>
     <string name="help_learning_fragment_1">These objects are represented in the form of 
        Scatter Plots. The first view of this mode shows a serie of Scatter Plots
        made by combining two attributes. This pair used to generate the
        Scatter Plot is mentionned into the corresponding thumb.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_2_0">When you have chosen a Scatter 
        Plot among those present on the grid, you can process it exactly 
        the same way as in the Game mode.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_2_1">After a split, two child nodes of 
        the current one are created in the tree and you can review the grid 
        but only with objects contained in one of the new node created. It is
        possible to continue the processing of the node if you estimate that it 
        is not pure enough. In the other case, the \"Stop\" button allows 
        visualizing the other nodes.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_3">A toggle button at the top-right 
        of the view enables the user to trace only horizontal or vertical lines. 
        This mode is used to compare trees built with machine learning 
        algorithm based on decision tree. At any time, some information are 
        available at the bottom of the screen. A local and a global error
        are provided.\nThe local error (LE) is the percentage of objects from the 
        current node that are not part of the majority class in the node. 
        Between parenthesis, there is the number of objects  
        included in the current node compared to the total number of objects in 
        the set.\nThe global error (GE) is the weighted sum of local errors of
        each leaf from the current tree. So, you have to minimize the local error
        for each node in order to reduce as far as possible the global error of
        the entire tree.</string>
     <string name="help_learning_fragment_4">Each error are shown for the 
        learning set (LS) and the test set (TS). These sets are disctinct subsets 
        of all objects from the database. The learning set is the part of objects that are 
        drawn on the screen. The test set is the rest of the objects that are
        hidden from the user in order to compare the model on non-processed data.
        \nDuring all the construction of the tree, the \"Tree view\" button makes 
        it possible to have a hierarchical view of it. So you can browse each node by 
        clicking on it. When you are at the current node, clicking on its
        ID allows the user to see the equation respected by all objects included in it.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_5_0">A progress bar also shows the progression
        of the processing. The light blue part represents the proportion of 
        visible objects on the screen. At the beginning, we are at 
        the root of the tree and we can see all the objects of the database. </string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_5_1">The grey part is not yet 
        shown objects. After a split, only some objects are visible on 
        the screen.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_5_2">When there is dark blue in the
        bar, it means that some objects have been stopped and are already
        a part of the model.</string>
    <string name="help_learning_fragment_5_3">A fully dark blue bar notifies the
         user that all objects are stopped and  distributed among the leaves 
         of the tree. At that moment, the tree is completely built and a model
         has been set up.</string>
    <string name="about_txt">The Treece project is a game with a purpose. 
        This application is a building tool for decision trees related to a 
        master thesis on machine learning. The objective of this work is to 
        estimate the capacity of humans to classify objects and compare it to 
        supervised machine learning algorithms.</string>
</resources>
